Register of the Fritz Machlup Papers, 1911-1983
Hoover Institution Archives
- BIOGRAPHICAL FILE, 1902-1982.
  - Subject file
    - Trips
      - Japan, 1970 April-June
        - Reports (Folder 20)
      - Australia, 1970 July-September
        - General (Folder 21)
        - Correspondence
          - Australian-American Education Foundation (Fulbright Commission). (Folder 22)
            See also Japan, 1970, Correspondence
          - With Australian universities and Reserve Bank of Australia (Folder 23)
      - Soviet Union, 1972. Correspondence and report (Folder 24)
      - Austria, 1973 February-June. Correspondence with Austrian-American Education Foundation (Fulbright Commission) and Committee on International Exchange of Persons (Folder 25)
      - United Kingdom, 1973 April. Correspondence with the United States-United Kingdom Education Foundation (Fulbright Commission) (Folder 26)
      - Luxemburg, 1973 May. Includes correspondence with the United States Embassy (Luxemburg) (Folder 27)
      - Austria, 1976. Correspondence with the United States Information Agency and schedules (Folder 28)
      - India and Pakistan, 1981. Correspondence and schedules (Folder 29)
  - Work progress reports (Folder 30)
- CORRESPONDENCE, CHRONOLOGICAL, 1973-1983
  - 1973 June-1974 October (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 1975 August-December (Folder 2)
  - 1975 November-1976 January (Folder 3)
  - 1976
    - January-March (Folder 4)
    - April-September (Folder 5)
    - October-December (Folder 6)
  - 1977
    - January-March (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
    - April-May (Folder 3)
  - 1977 June-1979 January (Folder 4)
  - 1979
    - February-September (Folder 5)
    - October-December (Folder 6)
  - 1980 (Folder 7)
  - 1981 (Folder 8)
  - 1982 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - 1983 (Folder 2)
- CORRESPONDENCE, ALPHABETICAL, 1933-1983
  - General
    - A-K (Box 21, Folder 3-13)
    - L-Z (Box 22, Folder 1-11)
  - Unidentified (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Abramovitz, Moses, 1934-1980 (Folder 2)
  - Abramson, Victor, 1947-1956 (Folder 3)
  - Academic Press, 1973-1983 (Folder 4)
  - Academy of Independent Scholars, 1981-1982 (Folder 5)
  - Accademia Nazionale dei Lincei (Enrico Cerulli), 1974-1978 (Folder 6)
  - Adams, John Clarke, 1943-1954 (Folder 7)
  - Adams, Walter, 1965 (Folder 8)
  - Adelman, M. A., 1967 (Folder 9)
  - Advisory Council on Economic Development (James E. Dugan), 1971 (Folder 10)
  - Alchian, Armen A., 1948-1977 (Folder 11)
  - Alderson, Wroe, 1958-1964 (Folder 12)
  - Alexander, Sidney S., 1964-1965 (Folder 13)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1973 (Folder 14)
  - Aliber, Robert Z., 1966-1968 (Folder 15)
  - Allais, Maurice, 1946-1977 (Folder 16)
  - Allen, Edward D., 1946 (Folder 17)
  - Allen, H. K., 1953 (Folder 18)
  - Allen, T. G. D.? 1938 (Folder 19)
  - Allen, William R., 1957-1975 (Folder 20)
  - Alon, Gabriel, 1966-1969 (Folder 21)
  - Alsberg, Carl L., 1935 (Folder 22)
  - Altman, Oscar L., 1964-1965 (Folder 23)
  - Altschul, Eugen, 1952 (Folder 24)
  - America in the Changing World (W. S. Woytinsky), 1948-1953 (Folder 25)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1961-1962 (Folder 26)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 196?-1975 (Folder 27)
  - American Bankers Association, 1960-1967 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - American Book Company, 1952 (Folder 2)
  - American Council of Learned Societies (Robert M. Lumiansky), 1978 (Folder 3)
  - American Economic Review
    - 1934-1939 (Folder 4)
    - 1940-1947 (Folder 5)
    - 1948-1974 (Folder 6)
    - 1981 (Folder 7)
  - American Enterprise Institute, 1971 (Folder 8)
  - American Philosophical Society, 1947-1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - American Red Cross, 1945 (Folder 2)
  - American Statistical Association, 1939 (Folder 3)
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company, 1962. Includes notes (Folder 4)
  - Ames, Edward, 1958-1973 (Folder 5)
  - Anderson, B. M., Jr., 1940 (Folder 6)
  - Anderson, Karl L. and Louise, 1934-1968 (Folder 7)
  - Andreae, C. A., 1973-1975 (Folder 8)
  - Androsch, Hannes, 1976 (Folder 9)
  - Angell, James W., 1939-1945 (Folder 10)
  - Anikin, Andrei, 1982 (Folder 11)
  - Annals (Philip G. Altbach), 1978 (Folder 12)
  - Antitrust Law and Economics Review, 1967-1968 (Folder 13)
  - Aoyama, Hideo, 1956-1966 (Folder 14)
  - Appleton-Century-Crofts, 1972 (Folder 15)
  - Ara, Kenjiro, 1956-1973 (Folder 16)
  - Arbeitsgemeinschaft Selbstandiger Unternehmer, 1959 (Folder 17)
  - Arlt, Carl T., 1936-1961 (Folder 18)
  - Arnavon, Cyrille, 1953 (Folder 19)
  - Arndt, Heinz W., 1970 (Folder 20)
  - Arndt, Helmut, 1959 (Folder 21)
  - Arnow, Kathryn S., 1981-1982 (Folder 22)
  - Aron, Raymond, 1975 (Folder 23)
  - Arrow, Kenneth J., 1954-1981 (Folder 24)
  - Aschheim, Joseph, 1960-1979 (Folder 25)
  - Aschinger, Franz, 1968-1975 (Folder 26)
  - Ash, Adrienne, 1975 (Folder 27)
  - Ashton, T. S., 1951-1952 (Folder 28)
  - Association of American Publishers, 1974 (Folder 29)
  - Association of American University Presses, 1978-1979 (Folder 30)
  - Associazione Bancaria Italiana.
    See Bancaria
  - Aubrey, Henry G., 1961-1968 (Folder 31)
  - Aufricht, Hans, 1953-1971 (Folder 32)
  - Augustus M. Kelley Publishers, 1952-1976 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Austria. Consulate (New York), 1975-1980 (Folder 2)
  - Austria. Embassy (United States), 1967-1980 (Folder 3)
  - Austria. Permanent Representative to the United Nations, 1974-1982 (Folder 4)
  - Austrian Children's Bicentennial Art Committee, 1976 (Folder 5)
  - Austrian College Society (Fritz Molden, Felix Pronay)
    - 1951-1966 (Folder 6)
    - 1967-1981 (Folder 7)
  - Bach, George Leland, 1948-1949 (Folder 8)
  - Bachmann, H., 1974 (Folder 9)
  - Bacic, Uros, 1961-1962 (Folder 10)
  - Badre, A. Y., 1956 (Folder 11)
  - Bagiotti. Tullio, 1962-1975 (Folder 12)
  - Bailey, Mrs. Stephen K., n.d. (Folder 13)
  - Balassa, Bela, 1970-1982. Includes correspondence re Bela Gsikos-Nagy (Folder 14)
  - Balassa, Edith, 1935-1962 (Folder 15)
  - Baldwin, R. E., 1946 (Folder 16)
  - Balogh, Thomas, 1934-1973 (Folder 17)
  - Baltimore Gas and Electric Company, 1955-1956 (Folder 18)
  - Banca Nazionale del Lavoro (Luigi Ceriani), 1966-1982 (Folder 19)
  - Bancaria (Gian Franco Calabresi), 1962-1972 (Folder 20)
  - Banco de Espana, 1971 (Folder 21)
  - Bancroft, Everett Clair, 1945 (Folder 22)
  - Bank of America (A. W. Clausen), 1972 (Folder 23)
  - Banker (Michael Green), 1966-1976 (Folder 24)
  - Barger, Harold, 1954-1964 (Folder 25)
  - Barre, Raymond, 1958-1976 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Bartell, Ernest, 1973 (Folder 2)
  - Basil Blackwell Publisher (H. L. Schollick), 1960-1962 (Folder 3)
  - Baster, James, 1949 (Folder 4)
  - Bator, Viktor, 1939-1940 (Folder 5)
  - Batt, W. F. J., 1970 (Folder 6)
  - Battelle (Centre de Recherche de Geneve), 1971 (Folder 7)
  - Baumol, William J., 1958-1982 (Folder 8)
  - Beach, E. F., 1954 (Folder 9)
  - Beck, Lewis White, 1954-1957 (Folder 10)
  - Becker, Gary S., 1965-1978 (Folder 11)
  - Beckhart, Benjamin H., 1933-1939 (Folder 12)
  - Beier, Friedrich-Karl, 1980 (Folder 13)
  - Bekerman, Gerard, 1974-1982 (Folder 14)
  - Bell, Daniel, 1969 (Folder 15)
  - Bell, J. F., 1958-1963 (Folder 16)
  - Bell, James Washington, 1934-1965 (Folder 17)
  - Beloit College, 1954-1958 (Folder 18)
  - Bender, Harry, 1953 (Folder 19)
  - Benham, Frederic, 1948-1949 (Folder 20)
  - Beniger, James R., 1982 (Folder 21)
  - Bennett, M. K., 1948 (Folder 22)
  - Bennion, E. G., 1944 (Folder 23)
  - Benoit-Smullyan, Emile, 1949-1951 (Folder 24)
  - Berger-Lieser, Helene, 1937-1961 (Folder 25)
  - Bergson, Abram, 1972-1977 (Folder 26)
  - Bergsten, C. Fred, 1968-1977 (Folder 27)
  - Bernstein, Edward M., 1956-1975 (Folder 28)
  - Bess, James L., 1981 (Folder 29)
  - Beth, Evert Willem, 1956-1958 (Folder 30)
  - Beza, Sterie T., 1963-1967 (Folder 31)
  - Bhagwati, Jagdish, 1966-1981 (Folder 32)
  - Bhatt, M. P., 1978 (Folder 33)
  - Biehl, Dieter, 1974 (Folder 34)
  - Bierstedt, Robert, 1966 (Folder 35)
  - Bigelow, Karl, 1935-1936 (Folder 36)
  - Bilimovich, Alexander D., 1951-1952 (Folder 37)
  - Binder, Paul, 1975 (Folder 38)
  - Birnbaum, Eugene A., 1967-1968 (Folder 39)
  - Bishop, Robert L., 1960 (Folder 40)
  - Bitros, George C., 1980 (Folder 41)
  - Black, Max, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Black, Stanley W., 1971-1982 (Folder 2)
  - Blackburn, Robert T., 1982 (Folder 3)
  - Bladen, Vincent W., 1950-1953 (Folder 4)
  - Blair, John M., 1950-1970 (Folder 5)
  - Blakiston Company.
    See Doubleday and Company
  - Blanco, Cicely Woods, 1962-1983 (Folder 6)
  - Blaug, Mark, 1971-1983 (Folder 7)
  - Blinder, Alan, 1980-1981 (Folder 8)
  - Blitz, Rudolph C., 1963-1974 (Folder 9)
  - Bloch, Fritz, 1952-1953 (Folder 10)
  - Bloch, Henry Simon, 1953-1975 (Folder 11)
  - Bloch, Victor, 1935 (Folder 12)
  - Bloom, Gordon Falk, 1938-1961 (Folder 13)
  - Bloomfield, Arthur I., 1963-1971 (Folder 14)
  - Board of Governors of the Federal Reserve System, 1937-1968 (Folder 15)
  - Boarman, Patrick M., 1962 (Folder 16)
  - Boas, George, 1958 (Folder 17)
  - Bober, M. M., 1955 (Folder 18)
  - Bochenski, Joseph, 1956 (Folder 19)
  - Boddy, Francis, 1975 (Folder 20)
  - Boddy, Margaret, 1964 (Folder 21)
  - Bode, Karl F., 1942 (Folder 22)
  - Bohi, Hans, 1951 (Folder 23)
  - Boletin del Banco Central de Venezuela, 1946 (Folder 24)
  - Bombach, Gottfried, 1962-1982 (Folder 25)
  - Bonbright, James C., 1956-1959 (Folder 26)
  - Bonn, M. J., 1939 (Folder 27)
  - Bonne, Alfred, 1952-1954 (Folder 28)
  - Boorstin, Daniel J., 1957 (Folder 29)
  - Bopp, Karl R., 1953-1970 (Folder 30)
  - Borlin, Max, 1956 (Folder 31)
  - Borts, George H., 1964 (Folder 32)
  - Bos, Dieter, 1971 (Folder 33)
  - Bosco, James J., 1976 (Folder 34)
  - Boskin, Michael J., 1974 (Folder 35)
  - Boulding, Kenneth E., 1946-1983 (Folder 36)
  - Bourdieu, Pierre, 1973 (Folder 37)
  - Bowen, Howard R., 1964 (Folder 38)
  - Bowen, William G., 1969-1978 (Folder 39)
  - Bowman, Mary Jean, 1945-1976 (Folder 40)
  - Boyer de la Giroday, Frederic, 1970 (Folder 41)
  - Bradford, W. D., 1947 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Brandstetter, Alois, 1972 (Folder 2)
  - Brandt, Karl, 1959-1960 (Folder 3)
  - Braun, Kurt, 1944-1975 (Folder 4)
  - Breit, William, 1974 (Folder 5)
  - Brems, Hans, 1947-1971 (Folder 6)
  - Breneman, David W., 1980 (Folder 7)
  - Brenner, Carliene, 1981 (Folder 8)
  - Briefs, Goetz A., 1949-1973 (Folder 9)
  - Briefs, Henry W., 1949-1973 (Folder 10)
  - Brigham Young University, 1975 (Folder 11)
  - British Broadcasting Corporation, 1968 (Folder 12)
  - British Journal for the Philosophy of Science (Donald A. Gillies, John Worrall), 1982 (Folder 13)
  - British Library, 1979 (Folder 14)
  - Broadley, J. Ashley, 1970-1971 (Folder 15)
  - Brofoss, Erik, 1970 (Folder 16)
  - Bronfenbrenner, Martin, 1946-1975 (Folder 17)
  - Brookings Institution (Robert D. Calkins, Robert Dorfman, Gary Fromm, Kermit Gordon, Joseph A. Pechman, Leonard Silk), 1942-1975 (Folder 18)
  - Brooklyn College (W. H. Steiner), 1942-1952 (Folder 19)
  - Brown, A. J., 1950 (Folder 20)
  - Brown, Francis C., 1957 (Folder 21)
  - Brown, Philip Stoddard, 1949 (Folder 22)
  - Brown, Ralph S., Jr., 1968 (Folder 23)
  - Brown, Samuel L., 1950 (Folder 24)
  - Browne, Martha Steffy, 1949-1982 (Folder 25)
  - Brownlee, O. H., 1948 (Folder 26)
  - Bryant, Ralph C., 1980 (Folder 27)
  - Brzeski, Andrzej, 1976 (Folder 28)
  - Buchanan, D. H., 1945-1946 (Folder 29)
  - Buchanan, Norman S., 1947 (Folder 30)
  - Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra Society, 1938-1941 (Folder 31)
  - Burgess, W. Randolph, 1937-1938 (Folder 32)
  - Burns, Carl R., 1959 (Folder 33)
  - Burns, Eveline, 1934-1935 (Folder 34)
  - Business Publications (Richard D. Irwin), 1937 (Folder 35)
  - Byrne, Brendan, 1979 (Folder 36)
  - Cairncross, Alec, 1954-1982 (Folder 37)
  - California Studies in Philosophy, Politics and Economics (William W. Bartley, III), 1974 (Folder 38)
  - Calkins, Robert D., 1937-1940 (Folder 39)
  - Calmann-Levy, Editeur, 1969-1975 (Folder 40)
  - Cambridge University Press, 1966 (Folder 41)
  - Campbell, Charles S., 1958 (Folder 42)
  - Canning, John B., 1934-1940 (Folder 43)
  - Canoyer, Helen G., 1946-1953 (Folder 44)
  - Canziani, Arnoldo, 1979 (Folder 45)
  - Capen, Samuel P., 1938-1950 (Folder 46)
  - Carlson, S., 1934-1935 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Carlson, Valdemar, 1943-1946 (Folder 2)
  - Carnegie Commission on Higher Education (Clark Kerr, Margaret S. Gordon), 1971-1977 (Folder 3)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York (Richard H. Sullivan), 1970-1971 (Folder 4)
  - Cartwright, Philip W., 1948-1958 (Folder 5)
  - Case Western Reserve University, 1975-1976 (Folder 6)
  - Cassady, Ralph, Jr., 1947 (Folder 7)
  - Cassels, John, 1962 (Folder 8)
  - Cato Institute, 1977 (Folder 9)
  - Cave, Evelyn, 1948 (Folder 10)
  - Caves, Richard E., 1963-1974 (Folder 11)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1965 (Folder 12)
  - Challenge, 1974-1979 (Folder 13)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States, 1943-1960 (Folder 14)
  - Chamberlin, Edward H., 1934-1961 (Folder 15)
  - Chandler, Lester V., 1957 (Folder 16)
  - Change, 1971-1979 (Folder 17)
  - Chapman, John M., 1934-1936 (Folder 18)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons
    - 1959-1964 (Folder 19)
    - 1965-1978 (Folder 20)
  - Cheek, M. Adolphus, Jr. and Jeannette, 1937-1979 (Folder 21)
  - Cheung, Steven N. S., 1981 (Folder 22)
  - Chipman, John S., 1949-1981 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Chittenden, George H., 1969-1971 (Folder 2)
  - Christ, Carl F., 1954-1973 (Folder 3)
  - Christenson, Carroll L., 1956 (Folder 4)
  - Chronicle of Higher Education, 1978-1979 (Folder 5)
  - Claassen, Emil-Maria (and Pascal Salin), 1967-1982. Includes correspondence with the German Marshall Fund of the United States (Folder 6)
  - Claremont Men's College (George C. S. Benson), 1955-1958 (Folder 7)
  - Clark, John Maurice, 1943-1945 (Folder 8)
  - Clarke, Stephen V. O., 1980 (Folder 9)
  - Clausing, Roth, 1942 (Folder 10)
  - Clemens, E. W., 1950-1951 (Folder 11)
  - Coale, Ansley J., 1974 (Folder 12)
  - Coase, Ronald H., 1954-1965 (Folder 13)
  - Coe, V. F., 1935 (Folder 14)
  - Cohen, Benjamin Jerry, 1964-1979 (Folder 15)
  - Colberg, Marshall R., 1968-1981 (Folder 16)
  - Cole, Arthur H., 1949 (Folder 17)
  - Colm, Gerhard, 1938-1965 (Folder 18)
  - Columbia University (Robert L. Carey, Leslie John), 1958-1963 (Folder 19)
  - Columbia University Press, 1940-1976. Includes correspondence with Ruby T. Norris (Folder 20)
  - Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1970 (Folder 21)
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1960-1981. Includes notes (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Academic Nondiscrimination and Integrity (Miro M. Todorovich)
    - 1971-1974 (Folder 2)
    - 1975 (Folder 3)
    - 1976-1979 (Folder 4)
  - Committee on Conceptual and Terminological Analysis (Fred W. Riggs)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - 1981-1983 (Folder 2)
  - Condliffe, John B., 1935-1944 (Folder 3)
  - Constantacatos, M. E., 1954 (Folder 4)
  - Cook, Thomas, 1951 (Folder 5)
  - Cooper, Richard N., 1968-1980 (Folder 6)
  - Copeland, Melvin Thomas, 1948 (Folder 7)
  - Copeland, Morris A., 1958 (Folder 8)
  - Corden, W. M., 1970 (Folder 9)
  - Cordt, Herbert, 1981 (Folder 10)
  - Cornell Alumni Committee for Balanced Education, 1971 (Folder 11)
  - Cornell University (Paul T. Homan, Alfred E. Kahn, Frank A. Southard, Jr.), 1940-1963 (Folder 12)
  - Cortney, Philip, 1950-1967 (Folder 13)
  - Coser, Lewis A., 1980 (Folder 14)
  - Coudenhove-Kalergi, R. N., 1941 (Folder 15)
  - Council for a Competitive Economy, 1979 (Folder 16)
  - Council of Economic Advisers, 1953-1966 (Folder 17)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1945-1980 (Folder 18)
  - Cowles Commission for Research in Economics, 1937-1938 (Folder 19)
  - Cremin, Lawrence A., 1970-1981 (Folder 20)
  - Cronbach, Lee, 1971 (Folder 21)
  - Crost, Joseph, 1941 (Folder 22)
  - Crum, W. Leonard, 1941-1950 (Folder 23)
  - Curzon, Victoria, 1974 (Folder 24)
  - Custis, Vanderveer, 1939 (Folder 25)
  - Daugherty, Carroll R., 1947 (Folder 26)
  - Davenport, John, 1961-1980 (Folder 27)
  - Davidson, J. Edward, 1938-1939 (Folder 28)
  - Davies, Jack L., 1968-1969 (Folder 29)
  - Davis, Bertram H., 1973-1974 (Folder 30)
  - Davis, Cameron J., 1943 (Folder 31)
  - Davis, Joseph Stancliffe, 1940-1964 (Folder 32)
  - Davis, Shelby Cullom, 1972-1974 (Folder 33)
  - Day, Alan C. L., 1963-1964 (Folder 34)
  - Deese, J., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Delivanis, Dimitrios J., 1962-1975 (Folder 2)
  - De Marchi, Neil, 1972-1973 (Folder 3)
  - Demaria, Giovanni, 1939-1957 (Folder 4)
  - Dennison, Stanley R., 1952-1963 (Folder 5)
  - Dernburg, Thomas F., 1960-1962 (Folder 6)
  - Despres, Emile, 1968 (Folder 7)
  - Deusenberry, James, 1948 (Folder 8)
  - Deutsches Institut fur Wirtschaftsforschung, 1959 (Folder 9)
  - De Vries, Margaret Garritsen, 1980-1981 (Folder 10)
  - De Vries, Thomas, 1976 (Folder 11)
  - De Vyver, Frank T., 1960-1969 (Folder 12)
  - Dickinson, Frank G., 1940 (Folder 13)
  - Dickinson, Z. C., 1934 (Folder 14)
  - Diederich, Helmut, 1977-1982 (Folder 15)
  - Dieterlen, Pierre, 1961-1968 (Folder 16)
  - Dietze, Gottfried, 1967-1976 (Folder 17)
  - Dillard, Dudley, 1950 (Folder 18)
  - Diplomatische Akademie, Vienna (H. Pfusterschmid), 1964-1979 (Folder 19)
  - Director, Aaron, 1946-1973 (Folder 20)
  - Dohtchevitch, Douchan D., 1939 (Folder 21)
  - Doi, Teruo, 1971-1975 (Folder 22)
  - Domar, Evsey D., 1948-1970 (Folder 23)
  - Dorrance, Graeme S., 1951-1952 (Folder 24)
  - Doubleday and Company, 1942-1961 (Folder 25)
  - Dreben, Burton S., 1956-1957 (Folder 26)
  - Drucker, Adolf Bertram, 1939-1941 (Folder 27)
  - Drucker, Peter F., 1937-1940 (Folder 28)
  - Dulles, Eleanor Lansing, 1946 (Folder 29)
  - Duncan, Acheson J., 1947 (Folder 30)
  - Duncan, George A., 1958-1964 (Folder 31)
  - Dunlop, John T., 1940-1968 (Folder 32)
  - Dupriez, Leon H., 1947-1964 (Folder 33)
  - Durrance, Professor, n.d. (Folder 34)
  - Earhart Foundation
    - 1953-1963 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - 1964-1976 (Folder 2)
    - 1977-1982 (Folder 3)
  - Eason, Warren W., 1956 (Folder 4)
  - Eber, Manuel, 1950 (Folder 5)
  - Eckert, James B., 1938-1941 (Folder 6)
  - Econometric Society, 1939-1970 (Folder 7)
  - Econometrica, 1934-1950 (Folder 8)
  - Economic Council of Canada, 1970 (Folder 9)
  - Economic Journal, 1970-1982 (Folder 10)
  - Economica (Basil S. Yamey), 1940-1960 (Folder 11)
  - Economics of Education Review (Elchanan Cohn), 1980 (Folder 12)
  - Economie Appliquee, 1960-1977 (Folder 13)
  - Economundo, 1975 (Folder 14)
  - Edelstein, Ludwig, 1953-1962 (Folder 15)
  - Edwards, Corwin D. and Trudi, 1944-1979 (Folder 16)
  - Eekelen, Lambrecht J. J. van, 1978 (Folder 17)
  - Egawa, Toshio, 1955 (Folder 18)
  - Ehrenfels, U. R., 1955 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Ehrlich, Otto H. and Edna, 1942-1979 (Folder 2)
  - Einaudi, Luigi and Ida, 1948-1962 (Folder 3)
  - Einaudi, Mario, 1935 (Folder 4)
  - Ellis, Howard S., 1935-1972 (Folder 5)
  - Ellsworth, P. T., 1939-1965 (Folder 6)
  - Elsevier Scientific Publishing Company, 1977-1978 (Folder 7)
  - Emminger, Otmar, 1965-1983 (Folder 8)
  - Encyclopaedia Britannica, 1944 (Folder 9)
  - Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences, 1961-1976 (Folder 10)
  - Enke, Stephen, 1949-1964 (Folder 11)
  - Epstein, Ralph C. (University of Buffalo), 1939-1959 (Folder 12)
  - Esteve, Tomas A., 1972 (Folder 13)
  - Ettinger, Karl Egmont, 1956 (Folder 14)
  - Eucken, Irene, 1954 (Folder 15)
  - Eucken, Walter, 1934-1948 (Folder 16)
  - Euromoney, 1972-1977 (Folder 17)
  - Evan, William M., 1976 (Folder 18)
  - Evans, George Heberton, Jr., 1958-1978 (Folder 19)
  - Exter, John, 1971 (Folder 20)
  - Fantozzi, Conrad T., 1940 (Folder 21)
  - Farber, Marvin, 1938-1964 (Folder 22)
  - Farkas, Edith, 1974-1976 (Folder 23)
  - Farmand (Trygve J. B. Hoff), 1965-1975 (Folder 24)
  - Farrar and Rinehart, 1939 (Folder 25)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of Minneapolis, 1953-1954 (Folder 26)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia, 1968 (Folder 27)
  - Feigl, Herbert, 1959 (Folder 28)
  - Feis, Herbert, 1942 (Folder 29)
  - Fekete, Janos, 1970-1972 (Folder 30)
  - Felderer, Bernhard, 1965-1974 (Folder 31)
  - Fellman, David, 1964-1970 (Folder 32)
  - Fellner, William J.
    - 1939-1965 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - 1966-1982 (Folder 2)
  - Ferber, Helen, 1970 (Folder 3)
  - Ferguson, Charles E., 1965-1970 (Folder 4)
  - Fernandes, Santiago, 1965-1975 (Folder 5)
  - Ferrari, Alberto, 1964 (Folder 6)
  - Ferrero, Romulo A. (and Romulo Ferrero Butters), 1965-1976 (Folder 7)
  - Fetter, Frank Albert, 1945 (Folder 8)
  - Fetter, Frank W., 1950-1968 (Folder 9)
  - Fidler, William P., 1972 (Folder 10)
  - Figgures, Frank E., 1970-1971 (Folder 11)
  - Filene, Edward A., 1934 (Folder 12)
  - Filippovski, E. E., 1973-1974 (Folder 13)
  - Financial Analysts Journal, 1967-1968 (Folder 14)
  - Financial Times, 1972-1977 (Folder 15)
  - Finger, J. M., 1969-1970 (Folder 16)
  - Fischer, Dietrich, 1978 (Folder 17)
  - Fisher, Irving, 1934-1946 (Folder 18)
  - Fisher, Paul, 1946-1952 (Folder 19)
  - Fisher, William Halder, 1950-1952 (Folder 20)
  - Fitch, Lyle C., 1946 (Folder 21)
  - Flanders, M. June, 1973 (Folder 22)
  - Fleischmann, Trude, 1949 (Folder 23)
  - Fleming, J. Marcus and Gloria, 1966-1976 (Folder 24)
  - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, 1935-1978 (Folder 25)
  - Follmi, Toni, 1975-1977 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Fondation Nationale des Sciences Politiques, 1972 (Folder 2)
  - Fondo de Cultura Economica (Victor L. Urquidi), 1950-1960 (Folder 3)
  - Forbes Magazine, 1974 (Folder 4)
  - Ford Foundation, 1954-1977 (Folder 5)
  - Fordham University, 1960-1961 (Folder 6)
  - Fordham University Press, 1960-1961 (Folder 7)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1935-1969 (Folder 8)
  - Fortune, 1955-1969 (Folder 9)
  - Foster, James F., 1938-1941 (Folder 10)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, 1947-1956 (Folder 11)
  - Foundation Press, 1936 (Folder 12)
  - Franck, Henry J., 1941-1942 (Folder 13)
  - Franck, Peter Goswyn, 1948 (Folder 14)
  - Frankel, S. Herbert, 1967 (Folder 15)
  - Frankfurter, A., 1941 (Folder 16)
  - Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung, 1964-1978 (Folder 17)
  - Frankfurter Gesellschaft fur Handel, Industrie und Wissenschaft, 1960 (Folder 18)
  - Free Press, 1968 (Folder 19)
  - Freie Universitat Berlin, 1959 (Folder 20)
  - Frenkel, Jacob A., 1974-1980 (Folder 21)
  - Frere, Jean, 1967-1976 (Folder 22)
  - Frere, Maurice, 1948-1962 (Folder 23)
  - Frey, Rene L., 1976 (Folder 24)
  - Friedman, Milton and Rose
    - 1935-1962 (Folder 25)
    - 1963-1982 (Folder 26)
  - Friedmann, Charlotte, 1938-1942 (Folder 27)
  - Friedmann, Maximilian, 1939-1941 (Folder 28)
  - Friedrich, Carl J., 1943-1954. Includes answers to questionnaire on postwar European reconstruction, 1943 (Folder 29)
  - Frisch, Helmut, 1976 (Folder 30)
  - Frisch, Ragnar, 1935-1940 (Folder 31)
  - Friss, Istvan, 1970-1972 (Folder 32)
  - Froehlich, Walter, 1938-1968 (Folder 33)
  - Froman, Professor, 1935 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Fromowitz, Wilhelm, 1938-1982 (Folder 2)
  - Frumkin, Gregory and Jacob G., 1951-1953 (Folder 3)
  - Fuchs, Ralph F., 1966-1971 (Folder 4)
  - Fujii, Shigeru, 1950-1955 (Folder 5)
  - Fujiti, Masahiro, 1969 (Folder 6)
  - Fukuda, Keitaro, 1965 (Folder 7)
  - Fulbright Commission, 1970-1973 (Folder 8)
  - Furth, J. Herbert, 1938-1982 (Folder 9)
  - Gaitskell, Hugh, 1955 (Folder 10)
  - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1949-1976 (Folder 11)
  - Gamba, Charles, 1955-1967 (Folder 12)
  - Gardner, Richard N., 1968 (Folder 13)
  - Gardner, Walter R., 1949-1964 (Folder 14)
  - Garfield, Eugene, 1981 (Folder 15)
  - Garver, Raymond, 1934 (Folder 16)
  - Gassler, Robert Scott, 1978 (Folder 17)
  - Gay, Charles R., 1937 (Folder 18)
  - Geiringer, Ernst, 1933-1938 (Folder 19)
  - Gelles, Herma, 1938 (Folder 20)
  - Gemmill, Paul F., 1936 (Folder 21)
  - General Learning Press, 1969-1980 (Folder 22)
  - General Motors, 1934 (Folder 23)
  - George Allen and Unwin (Publishers), 1978 (Folder 24)